Ramadan Kareem everyone, reporting live from Ghazza city, Ghazza.
Shortly after the illegal U.S.-Israeli attacks on Iran,
the Zionists took advantage of the moment to announce the indefinite closure of all borders here in Ghazza,
meaning that we are back to a total blockade.
We have about one week's worth of fresh food.
We're talking about a population of almost two million people
that are already suffering from acute malnutrition,
that survived six months of famine already.
We're preparing to possibly go back to being in famine.
Again, there has been no end date on when these closures will be lifted.
This is a total blockade of the Gaza Strip.
This isn't only affecting Ghazza.
They also announced military checkpoint closures in occupied Palestine.
The genocide here continues, and we have to be very clear, we have to continue to uplift it.
We can uplift multiple things at the same time.
We can talk about the illegal attacks on Iran and their right to sovereignty,
to protect themselves against the imperialist Epstein class.
And we can talk about the need to continue to fight for the end of genocide in Palestine, Congo, and Sudan.
The Israelis continue their airstrikes.
They've been bombing in Al-Barrej, in Al-Tofa.
Israeli military ships have been shooting at people on the beach in Han Yunus.
The genocide has not stopped.
It's just gotten a lot slower, and there's less media attention on what's been happening here.
But the bombings, the drones, the shelling by the military continue.
This is all being done simultaneously as the Zionists attack Lebanon
and forcibly displace over one million Lebanese from the southern border,
which should be very alarming because this is part of the Greater Israel Expansion Plan here in the region.
And all this is being fueled by stolen Venezuelan oil after the U.S. illegally invaded and attacked the sovereignty of Venezuela
so that they can control the oil and continue to fuel genocide and illegal forever wars.
Instead of that fuel being sent to Cuba, they are fighting U.S. imperialism and illegal, life-threatening U.S. sanctions.
We have to remember that all of these things are connected.
And these are intentional attacks on the axis of resistance that supports the Palestinian cause and Palestinian liberation.